<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lanta Nomads</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/</link><description>Recent content on Lanta Nomads</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://lantanomads.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beaches</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/beaches/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/beaches/</guid><description>Content coming soon — feel free to add your favourite beaches in data/beaches.md.</description></item><item><title>Coworking</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/coworking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/coworking/</guid><description>There are 3 coworking spaces in the area and lot&amp;rsquo;s of cafes you can work from.
Coworking spaces Kohub This is by far the biggest coworking space in Koh Lanta. It has a lot of space, good internet and a nice community.
Fika
Coworx
Cafes There are many cafes around the island where you can work from. Some popular ones include:
The Glass House
Escape Cafe</description></item><item><title>Food</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/food/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/food/</guid><description>Food Breakfast places Restaurants with good fish Shanti Shanti Beach House - Good fish, win and sunset meals. Best from 6PM-10PM.
Laanta Seafood
Birthday cakes Captain Bakery
The Living Room
The Glass House stopped selling cakes.
Delivery You can order food online on Lanta365.
Where to buy Item Shops Chia seeds Bonnie&amp;rsquo;s Deli, Lanta Mart Oats Lanta Mart</description></item><item><title>Health &amp; Beauty</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/health/</guid><description>Medical You can walk in to all clinics. Dr. Salarin is a good GP on Long Beach. For something more advanced with testing, Dr. Pad in Saladan is a good option. Thonburi Lanta offers 24-hour emergency care.
Dentists Lanta Dente - Only dentist on the island, on Khlong Dao road. Nails Cool Nail Studio
Barber and haircut Let me cut Barber - next to Slow Bar Caffetaria.</description></item><item><title>Visa</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/visa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/visa/</guid><description>Visa 93 countries get 60 days visa-free. That&amp;rsquo;s enough for most visitors. You can extend by 30 days at immigration if you want to stay longer, or apply for a tourist visa (60 days) before your trip.
Before you fly, fill out the Thailand Digital Arrival Card (TDAC). It&amp;rsquo;s required within 72 hours of arrival.
If you&amp;rsquo;re planning to stay and work remotely, look into the Destination Thailand Visa (DTV). It&amp;rsquo;s a 5-year multiple-entry visa with 180-day stays that can be extended by another 180 days.</description></item><item><title>Accommodation</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/accommodation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/accommodation/</guid><description>Options 1. Kohub Bungalows Use the contact link on KoHub.org.
2. Cheeky Monkey / Anna House Cheapest way to book is to message them on WhatsApp
3. Forest house 4. Phrae Ae appartments 5. Lanta Grand House Booking.com.
6. Morakot Resort Surprisingly Booking.com is much cheaper than what they quoted me on Whatsapp.
7. Baan Nok 8. The travelers friend bungalows 9. Baan long haad 10. Lanta Buddy Resort 11. Maisuree Lanta Resort-Long Beach https://www.</description></item><item><title>Activities</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/activities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/activities/</guid><description>Activities Massages Crypto near ozone Anchan Dreamy spa</description></item><item><title>Coffee</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/coffee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/coffee/</guid><description>Coffee Cafes Slow Bar Caffetaria - the best coffee on the island. Irregular opening hours. Not on Google Maps, but the pin is the correct location. You can see it with Street View.
Beans Slow Bar Caffetaria - the best coffee on the island. Irregular opening hours. Not on Google Maps, but the pin is the correct location. You can see it with Street View.
Oasis Yoga - sells beans in their shop</description></item><item><title>Drinks</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/drinks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/drinks/</guid><description>Drinks Craft Beer Devy Ale Cafe - Best craft beer selection on the island. Located at the end of Saladan road. Great selection of Thai craft beers (brewed in Cambodia/Laos due to Thai laws). Expect 230-240 baht per beer.
Bonnies Deli - Shop that sells a good selection of craft beers.
Wine Seven Seas at Pimalai Resort - Fine dining with extensive wine list.
Cocktails Sugggestions welcome!
Nice bars Pangea Beach Bar - Long Beach.</description></item><item><title>Where to buy</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/buy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/buy/</guid><description>Pillows Jimmy&amp;rsquo;s Plastic Shop
Ikea - Yes, there is Ikea in Thailand and for most things delivery costs are only 99 THB.
Decathlon - for inflatable pillows like this one.
Art supplies Thai Brand - just before turning to the bridge
Food See the Food page for where to buy food items and birthday cakes.
Coffee See the Coffee page for where to buy coffee beans and equipment.
Photos Kodak shop is the place to go for passport photos and for visa extenstions.</description></item><item><title>Fixing things</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/fixing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/fixing/</guid><description>Fixing things Laptops Ek (see sign in Kohub entrance) https://maps.app.goo.gl/YtSupSdZ7Adi6ghQ6?g_st=aw Phones https://maps.app.goo.gl/detkneyDxiTgNVJSA https://maps.app.goo.gl/9JCQawpnboWu6Lpq8?g_st=ic https://www.google.de/maps/place/lantamobiles(ANJ)/@7.6469089,99.0365148,544m/data=!3m1!1e3!4m6!3m5!1s0x304e03df42f929a7:0x1467c91a42bf1174!8m2!3d7.6484539!4d99.0372801!16s%2Fg%2F11h0y616rm?entry=ttu&amp;amp;g_ep=EgoyMDI1MDIwOS4wIKXMDSoASAFQAw%3D%3D Scooters Flat tires: https://maps.app.goo.gl/cSukRtbw65ANbrgo6</description></item><item><title>Parties</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/parties/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/parties/</guid><description>There is a more or less fixed schedule for the parties on the island. The big ones have a fixed day of the week. Some bars are a bit hidden but when they are the main party that night there will be torches outside on the main road to guide you there.
Monday Pub Quiz at the Irish Embassy
Irie Bar - Live music
Tuesday Pangea, starts at 21:00.
Wednesday Fusion Bar, starts at 21:00.</description></item><item><title>Sports</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/sports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/sports/</guid><description>Sports Gyms WM Fitness - Long Beach area. Modern gym with good selection of cardio equipment, resistance machines, and free weights. Also has a rig area with battle ropes, sandbags, kettlebells. Connected to William Muay Thai Stadium. Air conditioned. Day pass 200 THB. See Facebook for full pricing information.
Luke&amp;rsquo;s Gym - European style gym in Klong Khong, surrounded by jungle. Dumbbells up to 50kg, many machines. Very clean with separate changing rooms and showers.</description></item><item><title>Transportation</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/transportation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/transportation/</guid><description>Transportation Scooter rental You can rent scooters almost everywhere on the island. The price is around 250-300 THB per day, depending on the season and the condition of the scooter. If you rent longer than a week you&amp;rsquo;ll get a better price. For example 5000 THB per month.
Nare Scooter Rental Shop has nicer, newer and better scooters than most.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a driver&amp;rsquo;s license or you don&amp;rsquo;t feel comfortable driving a scooter, you can rent an e-bike from Koh Lanta Bike Rentals instead.</description></item><item><title>Money</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/money/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/money/</guid><description>Paying Paying with cash is the norm on the island. You can pay with credit/debit card in the bigger restaurants and shops but usually there is a fee and a minimum amount. Mobile payment apps with QR-codes like PromptPay and Moreta are becoming more popular but are still not widely accepted. And some can only be used by locals.
ATMs The Yellow ATMs will give you 30.000 THB, the others are limited to 20.</description></item><item><title>Random</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/random/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/random/</guid><description>11-7 Sound The beeps: YouTube
Hello Welcome: YouTube
Storage There is a seasonal storage service on the island: Lanta Box
Printing Scanning, Photocopying and Printing are free for up to five pages for Kohub members, beyond that, they charge a small fee for larger jobs.</description></item><item><title>Trips</title><link>https://lantanomads.com/trips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lantanomads.com/trips/</guid><description>Mangroves Enter the mangroves, pay the 20b entrance fee, they will try to get you to rent from them or get a guide, ignore that. Then carry on past the toilet, over the bridge, there&amp;rsquo;s a little restaurant on the left that rents yellow/red kayaks for 500b for 2 hours</description></item></channel></rss>